vive.com 2004-04-23

# Flash Horizon

Copyright ©1996, 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 2002. 2003 

Flash Horizon Inc.  
1600 Aimco Blvd. Unit 9  
Mississauga, Ontario CANADA L4W 1V1 

Except as otherwise indicated elsewhere in this publication, with respect to a particular portion, file, or document, any person is hereby authorized to view, copy, print, and distribute these documents 

Flash Horizon Inc. is committed to protecting your privacy. The following discloses our information gathering and dissemination practices for this web site: [www.flashorizon.com](http://www.flashorizon.com/)

**Information that FLASHLINE Gathers**

FLASHLINE gathers two types of information about users: 

> (1) Personal data provided through voluntary registration. Personal data may be requested when you sign up for FLASHLINE's personalized services or register for contests or other promotional programs offered on our service. We ask for this information in order to enhance your experience on our web site. This information might include member name, password, age, gender, ZIP code and/or country information. Except as described below, this information is not disclosed to parties other than FLASHLINE in any way that personally identifies you without your prior permission.
> 
> (2) Aggregated data which tracks users as a whole. Aggregated data tracks FLASHLINE user activity in general, and is not used to identify you personally. Aggregated tracking information helps us to determine which areas of our site users like and do not like based on traffic to those areas. FLASHLINE does not track what you read, but rather how well each page performs overall. This data helps us to continue to deliver a better service for you. We may disclose such aggregated information to third parties such as our advertisers and partners. 

**How Flash Horizon Inc. uses information**

FLASHLINE does not collect personally identifiable information about you except when you specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. FLASHLINE uses any personal information that's voluntarily given by you in order to enhance your experience, whether to provide interactive or personalized elements on the site or to better prepare future content based on the interests of our users. FLASHLINE also uses information that you voluntarily provide in order to send electronic updates and to let you participate in polls and message boards. 

You should be aware that when you voluntarily disclose personally identifiable information (e.g., user name, e-mail address) on the message boards on the FLASHLINE site, that information, along with any substantive information disclosed in your communication, can be collected and correlated and used by third parties and may result in unsolicited messages from third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of FLASHLINE. 

FLASHLINE will not disclose any information that personally identifies you to parties other than FLASHLINE without your consent. There are exceptions: 

> (1) When the purpose and manner of disclosure is clearly defined in advance.
> 
> (2)When we believe in good faith that disclosure is legally required or to protect our rights. 

**Cookies and Tracking**

You should be aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of FLASHLINE's Internet servers or through the use of "cookies". A "cookie" is a small text file that a web site can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate you ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and target advertising. Web sites commonly write a cookie to your hard drive when you visit them. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. Cookies don't identify you personally, but rather identify your computer when you visit our site. A cookie cannot read data off your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. 

You should be aware that FLASHLINE cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for FLASHLINE.  
If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, you should note that cookies may be necessary to provide you with certain features (e.g., customized account features) available on the FLASHLINE site. 

FLASHLINE uses cookies as a way to measure activity on the site in order to continually improve your experience. Generally, we use cookies to: 

> (1) Remind us of who you are and to access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver to you a better and more personalized service. FLASHLINE also uses cookies to store your zip code for other services. 
> 
> (2) Estimate the size of FLASHLINE's audience. Each browser accessing FLASHLINE is given a unique cookie which is then used to determine the extent of repeat usage, and to help target advertisements based on user interests and behavior. 
> 
> (3) Track your progress and number of entries in some of our promotions and contests. When a FLASHLINE-hosted promotion uses cookies, the information written to the cookie indicates the player's progress through the promotion, and may be used to track entries, submissions, and status in contests. 
> 
> (4) Measure certain traffic patterns, which areas of FLASHLINE's network of web sites you have visited, and your visiting patterns in the aggregate. We use this research to understand how our users' habits are similar or different from one another so that we can enhance your experience on the FLASHLINE web site. We may use this information to better personalize the content, banners, and promotions that you and other users will see on our sites. 

Advertising networks that serve ads onto FLASHLINE may also use their own cookies. 

FLASHLINE also collects IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our advertisers. In addition, FLASHLINE Mail includes IP addresses in outgoing mail message headers. 

**Flash Horizon Inc.’s Content Providers, Advertisers and Partners**

FLASHLINE will not provide your personal information to anyone outside of FLASHLINE except in the limited circumstances mentioned, and only then with your consent. However, FLASHLINE cannot control the practices of third parties, such as other partners and advertisers. FLASHLINE is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties. You should check the applicable privacy policy of such party when providing personally identifiable information. 

It is important to note that FLASHLINE contains many links to sites other than FLASHLINE, and that those sites may not follow the same privacy policies as FLASHLINE. This includes links from advertisers, content providers and partners who may use FLASHLINE's logo and/or style as part of a co-branding agreement. These sites may send their own cookies to you, and as a result, may collect data and ask for personal information that FLASHLINE would not. You should be aware that FLASHLINE cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties. 

**Children and Privacy**

FLASHLINE requests that children under 17 do not submit or post any information to the site without the consent of a parent or guardian. However, we will not request or knowingly collect from a child any information online that can be traced to the child, such as an email address, name, or information about the child's family. Unless a parent or guardian consents to such use in advance, FLASHLINE will not knowingly use information that a child provides to FLASHLINE for any marketing, selling or promotional purposes. 

**Your Consent**

By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by FLASHLINE. 

**Changes to Policy**

The foregoing policies are effective as of March 1, 2002. FLASHLINE reserves the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. 

* * *

Company |  Products |  Solutions |  Sales |  Support | Services | Site Map
